[{"answer": "I don't think it's an argument that either one of these men can win because it's so dependent, almost entirely dependent on events beyond their control.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Is anybody winning that argument?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "You know, the -- the problem is that everybody is a little bit right.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "I mean isn't that the reality, a stain on all your houses?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "How many men of that age shower with boys of 13, 14?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I don't think we're really facing up to our problems.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "But what is your feeling about what has gone wrong with America incorporated?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "You know, I would -- I still lean towards him, because I know nothing about -- I still don't feel I know anything about Romney.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Would you vote for him?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "And I never, ever thought that I would.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I just feel -- you know, he had a good first two years.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "And the main reason for that would be what?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Zach is now 28.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "He's how old now?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "You know, I would say around the ages -- you know, I don't really remember, maybe 10 to 12, he has a phenomenal memory.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "When did you first realize this?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean it is a little bit like that.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Is it like the character of Dustin Hoffman?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "The intention was not to rediscover my son.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What was the intention of this?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's about acceptance.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What did you learn about fatherhood that maybe surprised you when you went on this trip?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "He has -- he has some concept.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Or does he just judge you purely on your personal qualities as a father?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Yes, since the last time I saw you, I thought you would never invite me back.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a Chateau le Tour.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Chateau le Tour?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "They are not.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Are they called the Fallonettes?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Thanks, god.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "How do you jump this rock star shot?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "The new look -- I'm just losing --", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "The new look?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I just have this compilation of all this music and maybe it is going in my ahead a little bit.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Are you not taken so seriously as a rock star?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "\"Whip My Hair.\"", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Bruce Springsteen, I mean incredibly, you got him to cover Willis Smith's hit, right?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "The Boss.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "-- The Boss?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Is he serious?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Listen, it's a brilliant album.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "And it's like, if you think about it, when would he -- when would he ever see Bruce dressed like he was 30 years ago?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "It was one of these weird things.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "How did you persuade him to do that?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Or did you deliberately lose to her to try and get the --", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "It's just the joy of competition, you know?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "No, because we did everything inside the White House.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "-- with the president?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Well, the goal of this is to get children to get fit and workout and do --", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Do you think you're enhancing the reputation of your nation and its great leader by doing a sack race the East Room, a potato race?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "And you had a private meeting with the president before this -- the slow jam?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Well, the -- it's -- by protocol, they want you to meet the president alone, because you invited him, so you -- so I'm -- I have to be there in -- no -- no stage manager, no assistants, no Fallonettes, no one is allowed to --", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "How does that go?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "-- why would I impersonate someone with three minutes left --", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "-- who would it be?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Don't be so American literal about this.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "I want to show God my act?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "So this \"Call Me Maybe,\" even my kids back in England, who wouldn't necessarily know who you are, now know you're the guy from the \"Call Me Maybe\" clip, because two million hits on YouTube.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Can you get more index cards laid out?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't turn it down.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "Would you turn down the \"Tonight Show\" if you were offered it?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "Is it -- is it the Holy Grail?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "I think it's the story around it, but it's not.", "docId": "120613pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Hasn't it always been the Holy Grail as a -- as a talk show host in America?", "qSentId": 771}]